{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "26x^3 - 6x^2 + 21x - 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(x^4 - x^4) + (14x^3 + 12x^3) + (-10x^2 + 4x^2) + (11x + 10x) + (-5 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(x^4 + 14x^3 - 10x^2 + 11x - 5) + (-x^4 + 12x^3 + 4x^2 + 10x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 + 11x^3 - 9x^2 + 18x + 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(11x^4 - 4x^4) + (9x^3 + 2x^3) + (-2x^2 - 7x^2) + (6x + 12x) + (3 + 3)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(11x^4 + 9x^3 - 2x^2 + 6x + 3) + (-4x^4 + 2x^3 - 7x^2 + 12x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 + 4x^3 + 9x^2 + 15x + 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(11x^4 - 4x^4) + (-4x^3 + 8x^3) + (4x^2 + 5x^2) + (14x + x) + (5 - 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(11x^4 - 4x^3 + 4x^2 + 14x + 5) - (4x^4 - 8x^3 - 5x^2 - x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^4 - 13x^3 - 6x^2 + 8x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(15x^4 - 6x^4) + (-12x^3 - x^3) + (-13x^2 + 7x^2) + (8x) + (3 + 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(15x^4 - 12x^3 - 13x^2 + 3) + (-6x^4 - x^3 + 7x^2 + 8x + 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^4 + 9x^3 + 22x^2 + 13x - 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 + 10x^4) + (8x^3 + x^3) + (12x^2 + 10x^2) + (5x + 8x) + (-12 + 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-11x^4 + 8x^3 + 12x^2 + 5x - 12) - (-10x^4 - x^3 - 10x^2 - 8x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7x^4 - 5x^3 - 9x^2 - 12x - 27", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 - 4x^4) - (5x^3) + (-11x^2 + 2x^2) + (-3x - 9x) + (-12 - 15)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^4 - 11x^2 - 3x - 12) - (4x^4 + 5x^3 - 2x^2 + 9x + 15)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-18x^4 - 7x^3 - 17x^2 + 19x + 4", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 - 15x^4) - (7x^3) + (-12x^2 - 5x^2) + (12x + 7x) + (13 - 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^4 - 12x^2 + 12x + 13) - (15x^4 + 7x^3 + 5x^2 - 7x + 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 - 4x^3 + 8x^2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(x^4) + (-3x^3 - x^3) + (4x^2 + 4x^2) + (4x - 4x)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^3 + 4x^2 + 4x) - (-x^4 + x^3 - 4x^2 + 4x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4 - 19x^3 + 5x^2 + 3x + 18", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(12x^4 - 9x^4) + (-6x^3 - 13x^3) + (-7x^2 + 12x^2) + (10x - 7x) + (5 + 13)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(12x^4 - 6x^3 - 7x^2 + 10x + 5) + (-9x^4 - 13x^3 + 12x^2 - 7x + 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^4 + 8x^3 + 4x^2 + 21x + 16", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(5x^4 + 10x^4) + (11x^3 - 3x^3) + (-x^2 + 5x^2) + (12x + 9x) + (3 + 13)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(5x^4 + 11x^3 - x^2 + 12x + 3) + (10x^4 - 3x^3 + 5x^2 + 9x + 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^4 - 9x^3 - 3x^2 + 12x - 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 - 5x^4) + (-9x^3) + (4x^2 - 7x^2) + (6x + 6x) + (-11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(13x^4 - 9x^3 + 4x^2 + 6x - 11) - (5x^4 + 7x^2 - 6x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^4 - 19x^2 + 9x - 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-12x^4 + 8x^4) + (-8x^2 - 11x^2) + (9x) + (-6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-12x^4 - 8x^2 + 9x) + (8x^4 - 11x^2 - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^4 + 6x^3 + 6x^2 - 20x + 4", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 3x^4) + (-6x^3 + 12x^3) + (15x^2 - 9x^2) + (-9x - 11x) + (-6 + 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-6x^4 - 6x^3 + 15x^2 - 9x - 6) + (3x^4 + 12x^3 - 9x^2 - 11x + 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8x^3 + 8x^2 - 19x - 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(6x^4 - 6x^4) + (-4x^3 - 4x^3) + (3x^2 + 5x^2) + (-7x - 12x) + (-7 + 1)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(6x^4 - 4x^3 + 3x^2 - 7x - 7) + (-6x^4 - 4x^3 + 5x^2 - 12x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 - 12x^3 - 18x^2 - 12x - 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(14x^4 - 7x^4) + (-9x^3 - 3x^3) + (-8x^2 - 10x^2) + (-12x) + (-10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(14x^4 - 9x^3 - 8x^2) + (-7x^4 - 3x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x - 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14x^4 - 22x^3 + x^2 - 9x - 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(5x^4 + 9x^4) + (-12x^3 - 10x^3) + (12x^2 - 11x^2) + (3x - 12x) + (-13 + 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(5x^4 - 12x^3 + 12x^2 + 3x - 13) - (-9x^4 + 10x^3 + 11x^2 + 12x - 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-21x^4 + 17x^3 - 9x^2 - 12x - 13", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-8x^4 - 13x^4) + (7x^3 + 10x^3) + (-2x^2 - 7x^2) + (-9x - 3x) + (-5 - 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-8x^4 + 7x^3 - 2x^2 - 9x - 5) - (13x^4 - 10x^3 + 7x^2 + 3x + 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 - 7x^3 + 16x^2 - 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(7x^4) + (-x^3 - 6x^3) + (5x^2 + 11x^2) + (-6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-x^3 + 5x^2 - 6) + (7x^4 - 6x^3 + 11x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7x^4 + 7x^3 + 21x^2 - 11x - 14", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-4x^4 - 3x^4) + (x^3 + 6x^3) + (7x^2 + 14x^2) + (-6x - 5x) + (-3 - 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-4x^4 + x^3 + 7x^2 - 6x - 3) + (-3x^4 + 6x^3 + 14x^2 - 5x - 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-21x^3 + 11x^2 + 2x + 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 + 3x^4) + (-9x^3 - 12x^3) + (11x^2) + (-5x + 7x) + (-3 + 5)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^4 - 9x^3 + 11x^2 - 5x - 3) - (-3x^4 + 12x^3 - 7x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3 - x^2 + 12x - 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-5x^4 + 7x^4) + (x^3 - 3x^3) + (-4x^2 + 3x^2) + (-3x + 15x) + (2 - 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-5x^4 + x^3 - 4x^2 - 3x + 2) + (7x^4 - 3x^3 + 3x^2 + 15x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^4 - 8x^3 + 4x^2 - x", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-13x^4 - 12x^4) + (6x^3 - 14x^3) + (11x^2 - 7x^2) + (-9x + 8x) + (-3 + 3)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-13x^4 + 6x^3 + 11x^2 - 9x - 3) - (12x^4 + 14x^3 + 7x^2 - 8x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^4 - 16x^3 - 10x^2 - 6x - 13", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-8x^4 + 13x^4) + (-3x^3 - 13x^3) + (-3x^2 - 7x^2) + (-5x - x) + (-10 - 3)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-8x^4 - 3x^3 - 3x^2 - 5x - 10) - (-13x^4 + 13x^3 + 7x^2 + x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19x^4 - 8x^3 - 6x^2 - 16x + 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(12x^4 + 7x^4) + (-5x^3 - 3x^3) + (-6x^2) + (-8x - 8x) + (7 - 6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(12x^4 - 5x^3 - 8x + 7) + (7x^4 - 3x^3 - 6x^2 - 8x - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^4 - 4x^3 - 12x^2 + 9x + 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 5x^4) + (9x^3 - 13x^3) + (-10x^2 - 2x^2) + (-5x + 14x) + (-5 + 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-6x^4 + 9x^3 - 10x^2 - 5x - 5) + (5x^4 - 13x^3 - 2x^2 + 14x + 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-18x^4 + 8x^3 - 18x^2 - 10x - 20", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-12x^4 - 6x^4) + (4x^3 + 4x^3) + (-6x^2 - 12x^2) + (-5x - 5x) + (-9 - 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-12x^4 + 4x^3 - 6x^2 - 5x - 9) - (6x^4 - 4x^3 + 12x^2 + 5x + 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^4 - 12x^3 + 2x^2 + 10x + 22", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-7x^4 + 5x^4) + (-9x^3 - 3x^3) + (2x^2) + (x + 9x) + (8 + 14)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-7x^4 - 9x^3 + x + 8) + (5x^4 - 3x^3 + 2x^2 + 9x + 14)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^4 + 3x^3 - 6x^2 - 23x", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(14x^4 - 10x^4) + (14x^3 - 11x^3) + (9x^2 - 15x^2) + (-9x - 14x) + (-8 + 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(14x^4 + 14x^3 + 9x^2 - 9x - 8) - (10x^4 + 11x^3 + 15x^2 + 14x - 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^4 - 4x^3 + x^2 - 5x + 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 + 6x^4) + (-x^3 - 3x^3) + (-x^2 + 2x^2) + (x - 6x) + (10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-11x^4 - x^3 - x^2 + x + 10) + (6x^4 - 3x^3 + 2x^2 - 6x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 - 8x^3 - 14x^2 - 3x + 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(4x^4 - 3x^4) + (x^3 - 9x^3) + (-11x^2 - 3x^2) + (-8x + 5x) + (-2 + 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(4x^4 + x^3 - 11x^2 - 8x - 2) - (3x^4 + 9x^3 + 3x^2 - 5x - 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x^4 + x^3 - 21x^2 - 22x - 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-13x^4 - 3x^4) + (-10x^3 + 11x^3) + (-11x^2 - 10x^2) + (-10x - 12x) + (-6 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-13x^4 - 10x^3 - 11x^2 - 10x - 6) - (3x^4 - 11x^3 + 10x^2 + 12x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 + 2x^3 - 9x^2 + 26x - 12", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-5x^4 + 12x^4) + (15x^3 - 13x^3) + (4x^2 - 13x^2) + (11x + 15x) + (-5 - 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-5x^4 + 15x^3 + 4x^2 + 11x - 5) + (12x^4 - 13x^3 - 13x^2 + 15x - 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 + 9x^3 - 7x^2 + 17x - 23", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(8x^4 - 6x^4) + (-4x^3 + 13x^3) + (-2x^2 - 5x^2) + (12x + 5x) + (-13 - 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(8x^4 - 4x^3 - 2x^2 + 12x - 13) + (-6x^4 + 13x^3 - 5x^2 + 5x - 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^4 - 7x^3 - 6x^2 - 15x - 4", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 + 15x^4) + (-6x^3 - x^3) + (5x^2 - 11x^2) + (-8x - 7x) + (5 - 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-11x^4 - 6x^3 + 5x^2 - 8x + 5) + (15x^4 - x^3 - 11x^2 - 7x - 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^4 - 15x^3 + 3x^2 - 16x + 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 + 2x^4) - (15x^3) + (9x^2 - 6x^2) + (-8x - 8x) + (9 - 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(13x^4 + 9x^2 - 8x + 9) - (-2x^4 + 15x^3 + 6x^2 + 8x + 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14x^4 + 13x^3 + 17x^2 + 6x + 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 + x^4) + (11x^3 + 2x^3) + (9x^2 + 8x^2) + (6x) + (1 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(13x^4 + 11x^3 + 9x^2 + 1) + (x^4 + 2x^3 + 8x^2 + 6x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 + 16x^3 + 22x^2 + 22x + 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 7x^4) + (10x^3 + 6x^3) + (12x^2 + 10x^2) + (10x + 12x) + (-10 + 13)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-6x^4 + 10x^3 + 12x^2 + 10x - 10) - (-7x^4 - 6x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x - 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^4 - 5x^3 + 16x^2 - 2x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-9x^4 + 7x^4) + (-3x^3 - 2x^3) + (15x^2 + x^2) + (4x - 6x) + (2 + 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-9x^4 - 3x^3 + 15x^2 + 4x + 2) - (-7x^4 + 2x^3 - x^2 + 6x - 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^4 + x^3 - x^2 - 14x + 13", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(6x^4 + 4x^4) + (-12x^3 + 13x^3) + (-13x^2 + 12x^2) + (-x - 13x) + (12 + 1)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(6x^4 - 12x^3 - 13x^2 - x + 12) + (4x^4 + 13x^3 + 12x^2 - 13x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^4 - 9x^3 + 18x^2 + 4x - 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 + 15x^4) + (-6x^3 - 3x^3) + (13x^2 + 5x^2) + (14x - 10x) + (6 - 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-3x^4 - 6x^3 + 13x^2 + 14x + 6) + (15x^4 - 3x^3 + 5x^2 - 10x - 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6x^4 - 20x^3 - 8x^2 + 16x + 7", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 - 3x^4) + (-10x^3 - 10x^3) + (x^2 - 9x^2) + (3x + 13x) + (7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^4 - 10x^3 + x^2 + 3x) - (3x^4 + 10x^3 + 9x^2 - 13x - 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 - 16x^3 - 3x^2 - 5x - 9", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 + 13x^4) + (-5x^3 - 11x^3) + (x^2 - 4x^2) + (-5x) + (-9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-11x^4 - 5x^3 + x^2 - 9) + (13x^4 - 11x^3 - 4x^2 - 5x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^4 + 17x^3 + 12x^2 + 7x", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(11x^4 - 3x^4) + (10x^3 + 7x^3) + (12x^2) + (-5x + 12x) + (-7 + 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(11x^4 + 10x^3 + 12x^2 - 5x - 7) + (-3x^4 + 7x^3 + 12x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 + 20x^3 + 21x^2 + 8x + 15", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(9x^4 - 7x^4) + (14x^3 + 6x^3) + (12x^2 + 9x^2) + (13x - 5x) + (6 + 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(9x^4 + 14x^3 + 12x^2 + 13x + 6) + (-7x^4 + 6x^3 + 9x^2 - 5x + 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x^4 - 5x^3 + 15x^2 + x - 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(3x^4 - 12x^4) + (x^3 - 6x^3) + (7x^2 + 8x^2) + (4x - 3x) + (1 - 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x^4 + x^3 + 7x^2 + 4x + 1) - (12x^4 + 6x^3 - 8x^2 + 3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^4 - x^3 - 2x^2 + 11x + 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(2x^4 + 13x^4) + (6x^3 - 7x^3) + (7x^2 - 9x^2) + (8x + 3x) + (6 - 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x^4 + 6x^3 + 7x^2 + 8x + 6) - (-13x^4 + 7x^3 + 9x^2 - 3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^4 + 2x^3 + 12x^2 - 9x - 14", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-4x^4 + x^4) + (2x^3) + (x^2 + 11x^2) + (-12x + 3x) + (-8 - 6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-4x^4 + x^2 - 12x - 8) + (x^4 + 2x^3 + 11x^2 + 3x - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^4 - 2x^3 - 2x^2 + 9x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(x^4 + 14x^4) + (-2x^3) + (-7x^2 + 5x^2) + (9x) + (7 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(x^4 - 2x^3 - 7x^2 + 9x + 7) + (14x^4 + 5x^2 + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^4 - 18x^3 + 14x^2 - 4x - 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-5x^4 + 3x^4) + (-3x^3 - 15x^3) + (11x^2 + 3x^2) + (9x - 13x) + (10 - 12)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-5x^4 - 3x^3 + 11x^2 + 9x + 10) - (-3x^4 + 15x^3 - 3x^2 + 13x + 12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-22x^4 - 18x^3 - 9x^2 + 22x - 7", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 - 11x^4) + (-12x^3 - 6x^3) + (-4x^2 - 5x^2) + (13x + 9x) + (4 - 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-11x^4 - 12x^3 - 4x^2 + 13x + 4) - (11x^4 + 6x^3 + 5x^2 - 9x + 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^4 - 23x^3 + 17x^2 - 13x - 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n-(x^4) + (-10x^3 - 13x^3) + (7x^2 + 10x^2) + (-5x - 8x) + (-12 + 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-10x^3 + 7x^2 - 5x - 12) - (x^4 + 13x^3 - 10x^2 + 8x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 + 14x^3 + 14x^2 + 10x - 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(4x^4 - 2x^4) + (5x^3 + 9x^3) + (4x^2 + 10x^2) + (4x + 6x) + (-12 + 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(4x^4 + 5x^3 + 4x^2 + 4x - 12) + (-2x^4 + 9x^3 + 10x^2 + 6x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-18x^4 - 6x^3 + 6x^2 - 22x + 9", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-7x^4 - 11x^4) + (3x^3 - 9x^3) + (-7x^2 + 13x^2) + (-11x - 11x) + (-1 + 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-7x^4 + 3x^3 - 7x^2 - 11x - 1) + (-11x^4 - 9x^3 + 13x^2 - 11x + 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^4 + 7x^3 - 12x^2 + 14x - 8", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-12x^4) + (4x^3 + 3x^3) + (-8x^2 - 4x^2) + (14x) + (-2 - 6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-12x^4 + 4x^3 - 8x^2 - 2) + (3x^3 - 4x^2 + 14x - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^4 - x^3 + 8x^2 - 19x - 12", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(7x^4 + 13x^4) + (13x^3 - 14x^3) + (13x^2 - 5x^2) + (-11x - 8x) - (12)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(7x^4 + 13x^3 + 13x^2 - 11x) - (-13x^4 + 14x^3 + 5x^2 + 8x + 12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^4 - 12x^3 - 6x^2 - x + 12", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-2x^4 + 8x^4) + (-12x^3) + (-6x^2) + (4x - 5x) + (-3 + 15)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-2x^4 + 4x - 3) + (8x^4 - 12x^3 - 6x^2 - 5x + 15)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19x^4 + 13x^3 - 5x^2 - 16x + 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(8x^4 + 11x^4) + (12x^3 + x^3) + (3x^2 - 8x^2) + (-8x - 8x) + (-1 + 6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(8x^4 + 12x^3 + 3x^2 - 8x - 1) + (11x^4 + x^3 - 8x^2 - 8x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13x^4 - 19x^3 + 15x^2 + 27x + 23", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-8x^4 - 5x^4) + (-7x^3 - 12x^3) + (7x^2 + 8x^2) + (15x + 12x) + (11 + 12)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-8x^4 - 7x^3 + 7x^2 + 15x + 11) + (-5x^4 - 12x^3 + 8x^2 + 12x + 12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 - 17x^3 + 4x^2 - 27x + 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(10x^4 - 8x^4) + (-3x^3 - 14x^3) + (10x^2 - 6x^2) + (-13x - 14x) + (12 - 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(10x^4 - 3x^3 + 10x^2 - 13x + 12) - (8x^4 + 14x^3 + 6x^2 + 14x + 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "26x^4 + 12x^3 + 18x^2 + 11x - 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 + 13x^4) + (11x^3 + x^3) + (11x^2 + 7x^2) + (3x + 8x) + (-6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(13x^4 + 11x^3 + 11x^2 + 3x - 6) - (-13x^4 - x^3 - 7x^2 - 8x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^4 - x^3 - x^2 + 12x + 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(2x^4 - 5x^4) + (-8x^3 + 7x^3) + (-11x^2 + 10x^2) + (12x) + (10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x^4 - 8x^3 - 11x^2 + 10) - (5x^4 - 7x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11x^4 + 13x^3 + 11x^2 + 3x - 13", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(x^4 + 10x^4) + (-2x^3 + 15x^3) + (7x^2 + 4x^2) + (7x - 4x) + (-5 - 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(x^4 - 2x^3 + 7x^2 + 7x - 5) + (10x^4 + 15x^3 + 4x^2 - 4x - 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13x^4 + 21x^3 - 5x^2 + 20x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(8x^4 + 5x^4) + (12x^3 + 9x^3) + (5x^2 - 10x^2) + (11x + 9x) + (11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(8x^4 + 12x^3 + 5x^2 + 11x + 11) - (-5x^4 - 9x^3 + 10x^2 - 9x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^4 - 16x^3 - x^2 - 25x - 13", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-11x^4 - 14x^4) + (-7x^3 - 9x^3) + (5x^2 - 6x^2) + (-10x - 15x) + (-6 - 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-11x^4 - 7x^3 + 5x^2 - 10x - 6) - (14x^4 + 9x^3 + 6x^2 + 15x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4 - 15x^3 - 13x^2 - 11x - 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(8x^4 - 5x^4) + (-12x^3 - 3x^3) + (-13x^2) + (-6x - 5x) + (-3)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(8x^4 - 12x^3 - 13x^2 - 6x - 3) + (-5x^4 - 3x^3 - 5x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-14x^4 - 18x^3 - 14x^2 + 7x - 7", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 - 8x^4) + (-9x^3 - 9x^3) + (-11x^2 - 3x^2) + (13x - 6x) + (-10 + 3)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-6x^4 - 9x^3 - 11x^2 + 13x - 10) - (8x^4 + 9x^3 + 3x^2 + 6x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10x^4 - 6x^3 + 7x^2 + 6x + 12", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-2x^4 - 8x^4) - (6x^3) + (-x^2 + 8x^2) + (-x + 7x) + (10 + 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-2x^4 - x^2 - x + 10) - (8x^4 + 6x^3 - 8x^2 - 7x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-24x^4 + x^3 - 5x^2 - 16x - 7", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-9x^4 - 15x^4) + (x^3) + (-5x^2) + (-9x - 7x) + (2 - 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-9x^4 - 5x^2 - 9x + 2) - (15x^4 - x^3 + 7x + 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 + 21x^3 + 3x^2 + 13x - 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(2x^4 - x^4) + (10x^3 + 11x^3) + (-4x^2 + 7x^2) + (5x + 8x) + (-13 + 2)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(2x^4 + 10x^3 - 4x^2 + 5x - 13) + (-x^4 + 11x^3 + 7x^2 + 8x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 + 4x^3 + 7x^2 - 9x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 7x^4) + (-x^3 + 5x^3) + (9x^2 - 2x^2) + (-12x + 3x) + (3 + 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-6x^4 - x^3 + 9x^2 - 12x + 3) + (7x^4 + 5x^3 - 2x^2 + 3x + 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11x^4 + 12x^3 + 19x^2 + 11x + 22", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-2x^4 - 9x^4) + (13x^3 - x^3) + (4x^2 + 15x^2) + (7x + 4x) + (14 + 8)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-2x^4 + 13x^3 + 4x^2 + 7x + 14) + (-9x^4 - x^3 + 15x^2 + 4x + 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13x^4 + 2x^3 - 2x^2 + 9x + 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-13x^4) + (4x^3 - 2x^3) + (-5x^2 + 3x^2) + (9x) + (5)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(4x^3 - 5x^2 + 9x) + (-13x^4 - 2x^3 + 3x^2 + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 - 7x^3 + 3x^2 - 10x - 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-5x^4 + 12x^4) + (6x^3 - 13x^3) + (3x^2) - (10x) + (-10 - 1)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-5x^4 + 6x^3 + 3x^2 - 10) - (-12x^4 + 13x^3 + 10x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^4 + 3x^3 + 7x + 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 - 9x^4) + (3x^3) + (10x^2 - 10x^2) + (x + 6x) + (-3 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(13x^4 + 10x^2 + x - 3) + (-9x^4 + 3x^3 - 10x^2 + 6x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^4 + 7x^3 - 8x^2 + 15x - 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-4x^4) + (15x^3 - 8x^3) + (-4x^2 - 4x^2) + (9x + 6x) + (3 - 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-4x^4 + 15x^3 - 4x^2 + 9x + 3) - (8x^3 + 4x^2 - 6x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11x^3 - 4x^2 - 11x + 8", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 6x^4) + (2x^3 - 13x^3) + (3x^2 - 7x^2) + (-11x) + (15 - 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-6x^4 + 2x^3 + 3x^2 + 15) + (6x^4 - 13x^3 - 7x^2 - 11x - 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11x^4 + 18x^3 - 4x^2 + 15x - 7", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n-(11x^4) + (6x^3 + 12x^3) + (-3x^2 - x^2) + (5x + 10x) - (7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(6x^3 - 3x^2 + 5x) - (11x^4 - 12x^3 + x^2 - 10x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 + 5x^3 - 3x^2 - 17x + 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(14x^4 - 7x^4) + (13x^3 - 8x^3) + (-11x^2 + 8x^2) + (-4x - 13x) + (8 - 5)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(14x^4 + 13x^3 - 11x^2 - 4x + 8) - (7x^4 + 8x^3 - 8x^2 + 13x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11x^4 - 5x^3 - 3x^2 - 14x + 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-12x^4 + x^4) + (3x^3 - 8x^3) + (-6x^2 + 3x^2) + (-5x - 9x) + (4 - 1)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-12x^4 + 3x^3 - 6x^2 - 5x + 4) + (x^4 - 8x^3 + 3x^2 - 9x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13x^4 + 6x^2 - 21x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(3x^4 + 10x^4) + (2x^3 - 2x^3) + (3x^2 + 3x^2) + (-12x - 9x) + (1 + 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(3x^4 + 2x^3 + 3x^2 - 12x + 1) + (10x^4 - 2x^3 + 3x^2 - 9x + 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4 - 20x^3 + 12x^2 + 14x + 11", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 + 7x^4) + (-11x^3 - 9x^3) + (3x^2 + 9x^2) + (10x + 4x) + (-3 + 14)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-6x^4 - 11x^3 + 3x^2 + 10x - 3) + (7x^4 - 9x^3 + 9x^2 + 4x + 14)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-17x^4 + 3x^3 + 3x^2 + 4x + 8", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-12x^4 - 5x^4) + (-2x^3 + 5x^3) + (-8x^2 + 11x^2) + (-5x + 9x) + (4 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-12x^4 - 2x^3 - 8x^2 - 5x + 4) + (-5x^4 + 5x^3 + 11x^2 + 9x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "29x^4 - 9x^3 - 9x^2 + 6x + 24", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(14x^4 + 15x^4) + (-10x^3 + x^3) + (-11x^2 + 2x^2) + (3x + 3x) + (10 + 14)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(14x^4 - 10x^3 - 11x^2 + 3x + 10) + (15x^4 + x^3 + 2x^2 + 3x + 14)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7x^4 + 3x^3 - 18x^2 - 7x + 2", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-3x^4 - 4x^4) + (10x^3 - 7x^3) + (-13x^2 - 5x^2) + (-8x + x) + (11 - 9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-3x^4 + 10x^3 - 13x^2 - 8x + 11) - (4x^4 + 7x^3 + 5x^2 - x + 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11x^4 - 20x^3 - 4x^2 - 21x - 1", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-5x^4 - 6x^4) + (-9x^3 - 11x^3) + (-4x^2) + (-13x - 8x) + (-5 + 4)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-5x^4 - 9x^3 - 4x^2 - 13x - 5) - (6x^4 + 11x^3 + 8x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "24x^4 - 12x^3 - 3x^2 + 18", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(14x^4 + 10x^4) + (x^3 - 13x^3) + (9x^2 - 12x^2) + (9x - 9x) + (7 + 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(14x^4 + x^3 + 9x^2 + 9x + 7) - (-10x^4 + 13x^3 + 12x^2 + 9x - 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13x^4 + 15x^3 - 5x^2 - 8x - 10", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-x^4 - 12x^4) + (6x^3 + 9x^3) + (-10x^2 + 5x^2) + (-13x + 5x) + (-4 - 6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-x^4 + 6x^3 - 10x^2 - 13x - 4) + (-12x^4 + 9x^3 + 5x^2 + 5x - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^4 + 3x^3 + 7x^2 + 4x - 9", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(8x^4 - 2x^4) + (6x^3 - 3x^3) + (10x^2 - 3x^2) + (x + 3x) + (-9)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(8x^4 + 6x^3 + 10x^2 + x - 9) + (-2x^4 - 3x^3 - 3x^2 + 3x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^4 - 3x^3 - 13x^2 + 10x + 12", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-9x^4 + 14x^4) + (-3x^3) + (-8x^2 - 5x^2) + (-2x + 12x) + (5 + 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-9x^4 - 8x^2 - 2x + 5) + (14x^4 - 3x^3 - 5x^2 + 12x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13x^4 - 18x^3 - 6x^2 + 23x", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-4x^4 - 9x^4) + (-9x^3 - 9x^3) + (-9x^2 + 3x^2) + (13x + 10x) + (11 - 11)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-4x^4 - 9x^3 - 9x^2 + 13x + 11) + (-9x^4 - 9x^3 + 3x^2 + 10x - 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^4 + 13x^3 - 14x^2 - 8x - 14", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(6x^4) + (7x^3 + 6x^3) + (-8x^2 - 6x^2) + (2x - 10x) + (1 - 15)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(6x^4 + 7x^3 - 8x^2 + 2x + 1) - (-6x^3 + 6x^2 + 10x + 15)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x^4 - 9x^3 - 3x^2 - 2x + 4", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(x^4 - 10x^4) + (-7x^3 - 2x^3) + (8x^2 - 11x^2) + (6x - 8x) + (11 - 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(x^4 - 7x^3 + 8x^2 + 6x + 11) - (10x^4 + 2x^3 + 11x^2 + 8x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^4 + 15x^3 + 9x^2 + 16x - 5", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(6x^4 - 10x^4) + (2x^3 + 13x^3) + (6x^2 + 3x^2) + (13x + 3x) + (-5)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(6x^4 + 2x^3 + 6x^2 + 13x - 5) + (-10x^4 + 13x^3 + 3x^2 + 3x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3 - 8x^2 - 3x - 19", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(2x^4) + (6x^3 - 8x^3) + (-4x^2 - 4x^2) + (-4x + x) + (-12 - 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x^4 + 6x^3 - 4x^2 - 4x - 12) - (8x^3 + 4x^2 - x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-18x^4 + 15x^3 - 6x^2 + 9x - 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-6x^4 - 12x^4) + (14x^3 + x^3) + (-2x^2 - 4x^2) + (-3x + 12x) + (9 - 15)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(-6x^4 + 14x^3 - 2x^2 - 3x + 9) - (12x^4 - x^3 + 4x^2 - 12x + 15)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^4 - 6x^3 - 12x^2 - 10x + 3", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(10x^4) + (-5x^3 - x^3) + (-13x^2 + x^2) + (-8x - 2x) + (-4 + 7)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(10x^4 - 5x^3 - 13x^2 - 8x - 4) - (x^3 - x^2 + 2x - 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x^4 + 18x^3 + 13x^2 - 5x + 6", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(5x^4 - 14x^4) + (11x^3 + 7x^3) + (5x^2 + 8x^2) + (-12x + 7x) + (6)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(5x^4 + 11x^3 + 5x^2 - 12x) - (14x^4 - 7x^3 - 8x^2 - 7x - 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^4 + 9x^3 - 19x^2 - 12x - 22", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(3x^4 + 2x^4) + (9x^3) + (-6x^2 - 13x^2) + (-3x - 9x) + (-9 - 13)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(3x^4 - 6x^2 - 3x - 9) + (2x^4 + 9x^3 - 13x^2 - 9x - 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^4 + 17x^3 + 18x^2 + 9x + 27", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(-8x^4 + 15x^4) + (5x^3 + 12x^3) + (14x^2 + 4x^2) + (5x + 4x) + (14 + 13)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Add:\n(-8x^4 + 5x^3 + 14x^2 + 5x + 14) + (15x^4 + 12x^3 + 4x^2 + 4x + 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19x^4 - 16x^3 - 5x^2 + 14x", "explanation": "Group the variables of the same degree together\n(13x^4 + 6x^4) + (-6x^3 - 10x^3) + (-7x^2 + 2x^2) + (3x + 11x) + (10 - 10)\nCombine the like terms to achieve a polynomial with just one coefficient per term", "question": "Subtract:\n(13x^4 - 6x^3 - 7x^2 + 3x + 10) - (-6x^4 + 10x^3 - 2x^2 - 11x + 10)", "type": "text"}
]}